

22. Princess Residence (22B-01).
Jalan Raja Mahmud,
50300 Kampung Baru,
Kuala Lumpur
+60 19-779 9074
aisyahhanifiah@live.com

PROFILE

Name: Nur Aisyah binti Mohd Hanifiah Date of Birth: 16 April 1996 IC: 960416-10-6422

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I find joy in creating visuals that are able to engage with people effectively while fulfilling the aesthetics of each graphic element. Based on my past experiences being a graphic designer,

I learnt a lot about how each graphics and type could influence the viewers. It is that everywhere I go I would think to myself on how people could improve their marketing materials.

I do work well both as a member of a team and in isolation with high attention to detail.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Amber & Sparkles | September 2016 - current

- Creating graphics based on tasks given and meeting deadlines
- Developed a strong attention to details towards each task.

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

The Pixel Things | August 2016 - current

- Founder of The Pixel Things (Instagram: @thepixelthings)
- Manage projects, customers and meeting deadlines

AMELIE THINGS: E-COMMERCE WEBSITE

PHP Programming Mini Project | January 2016

- Developed an e-commerce website
- With features such as user log in, cart, checkout, etc.

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Universiti Kuala Lumpur (MIIT) | Jun 2014 - current

Current CGPA: 3.99

Previous semester GPA: 4.00

SIJIL PELAJARAN MALAYSIA

Sekolah Tun Fatimah | 2012 - 2013

Pure science

Grade: 5A+ 4A

PENILAIAN MENENGAH RENDAH

Sekolah Tun Fatimah | 2009-2011

Grade: 8A

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator PHP HTML & CSS WordPress Bootstrap MySQL

KNOWLEDGE

JAVA C# C++ VB.NET ASP.NET

PERSONAL SKILLS

TEAMWORK	
CREATIVITY	_
ORGANIZATION	
COMMUNICATION	
INDEPENDENT	

REFERENCES

NORHATTA BINTI MOHD | Academic Advisor +60 12-209 3859 | norhatta@unikl.edu.my

MUHAMMAD ASHRAF BIN ROSLAN | Amber & Sparkles +60 18-663 7097 | order.amberandsparkles@gmail.com

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Malay

Enalish